http://www.femailcreations.com/pages/privacy-policy

0
My Cart Item(s)
Search
"Close (esc)"
Privacy & SecurityThis web site is owned and operated by Femail Creations. We understand that many visitors to our web site are concerned about the information they provide and how we handle that information. The purpose of this Privacy & Security Statement is to address those concerns, but please contact us if you have any questions. We may make changes to this Privacy & Security Statement from time to time, you should check this Statement periodically. The date of posting this statement is 08/11/16 and this Privacy & Security Statement replaces any pervious version.
For purposes of this Privacy & Security Statement, the term “web site” includes all Femail Creations internet sites and mobile applications.
SecuritySecuring your information is a company priority, we use reasonable security measures to help protect your personal information. Your account information is protected by the password you use to access your online account. We use technology called Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption, which is the standard for performing secure transactions. When you make a purchase, request a catalog or create an account on our Web site, your transactional information is transmitted in a safe, encrypted format.
Our web site and social media pages may provide links to other web sites owned or operated by third parties as a convenience to our visitors. We have no control over linked sites and make no representations about any content or material available at these locations. We are not responsible for the content of those sites. Links are not intended to imply sponsorship, affiliation, or endorsement. Such linked sites may have privacy policies that differ from this Privacy Statement. The terms of this Privacy Statement do not apply to any third-party web sites that are accessed from links found on our web site or social media pages.
Information We Share with Others and Your Privacy RightsWe contract with other companies to provide certain services, including shipping, name and address verification, email distribution, market research, third party advertising, promotions management and payment processing (to view PayPal's privacy policy, please visit https://www.paypal.com/privacy). We provide these companies with only the information they need to perform their services and work closely with them to ensure that your privacy is respected and protected. These companies are prohibited by contract from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than us.
From time to time, we make our mailing list (names and addresses only) and general shopping activity available to reputable companies whose products or services we believe will be of interest to you and whose privacy practices meet the Direct Marketing Association's privacy standards. We do not share email addresses for this purpose. If you do not want to receive mailings from other reputable companies and prefer that we do not share any information with these companies, please contact us.
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, or when required by law to do so. We may also share information with companies assisting in fraud protection or investigation. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.
Information We CollectWe maintain the data that you provide us, along with a record of your purchases, in a secure database. To best serve you, we may combine this information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources, including our credit card issuer whose policies meet the Direct Marketing Association's privacy standards.
We also gather information about how visitors navigate through our web site by using clickstream data gathered with "cookies" and other online tools such as "pixel tags."
Information We Provide to YouWe offer choices about the types of information you receive from us. If you prefer not to receive catalogs or email updates, or if you prefer to receive them less frequently, please visit the My Account section of our site(s) or contact us at the address shown below. You can also unsubscribe from our email updates using the link provided in each edition of the email. Femail Creations218 Massengale RoadClarksville, AR 72830
Cookies and Pixel TagsA cookie is a small data file stored by your web browser on your computer. Cookies enable you to place an order on our web site. They also allow us to enhance and personalize your online shopping experience, so the information you receive is more relevant to you.
For example, we use cookies to:
Remember what items are in your shopping cart
Recognize you when you return to our web site
Enables faster checkout, if you have created an account at llbean.com
Study how our customers navigate through our web site and which products they request in site searches
Deliver personalized marketing messages
We also use pixel tags – tiny graphic images – to tell us what parts of our web site you have visited or to measure the effectiveness of any searches you may do on our site. Pixel tags also enable us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.
We may also contract with other companies who use cookies or other online tools such as pixel tags to measure the performance of a marketing effort on our behalf. We prohibit these companies from using this information for their own marketing purposes or from sharing this information with anyone other than us.
We also contract with third party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf across the internet. To do this, they will collect anonymous information about your visits to our web site and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other web sites to target advertisements. These targeted advertisements may appear on other sites that you visit. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a cookie or pixel tag – industry standard technology used by most major web sites. No personally identifiable information is collected in this process.
How We Use EmailWhen you provide us your email address, we will email you as necessary to process your order, respond to a request or provide customer service. For example, after you place an order, you will receive an email confirmation and, in most cases, an email with package tracking information. Recipients of our email gift cards will receive an email notifying them of the gift and instructing them how to redeem it.
We may also send promotional emails about products, special offers, services or events we believe may be of interest to you. It is our intent to send promotional emails only to those who wish to receive them. We provide instructions on how to unsubscribe in each email and within the My Account section of our web site.
ChildrenChildren's privacy is important to us. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age. Any communication we get that is identified as being from a child under 13 will not be kept.
"Close (esc)"
